uli.org 2019-08-22

# Privacy Policy | Urban Land Institute

ULI promotes an open exchange of information, including mistakes made and lessons learned. To create a safe forum in which to exchange ideas and disseminate information or knowledge on practices, ULI and its members demand a mutual respect for privacy, strict confidentiality of proprietary information, and copyright protection.

**Our promise to you**

ULI will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit ULI websites unless you affirmatively choose to provide such information.

**What information is collected about me when I visit ULI websites? How is it used?**

When you visit our site, we automatically collect and store only the following information about you, none of which is personally identifiable:

  * Your host name or IP address
  * The domain from which you access our site
  * The day, month, and year you access our site.
  * Your Device user agent identity (providing browser type, operating system type)

We use this information to calculate the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to future visitors. We do not sell or transfer to third parties any of the information collected automatically from every visitor.

**What about “cookies”?**

ULI uses cookies to store and track certain information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. In general, ULI uses cookies to store your logged-in status for members-only and subscription areas of our site, and to keep track of your order as you make online purchases via our e-commerce system.  [Read more about ULI’s use of cookies on our websites.](https://uli.org/legal-notices/cookie-policy/)

If you browse ULI websites with the cookies option turned off, you may not be able to use various features of our sites.

**How secure is my credit card information and any personal information I transmit?**

When you make online purchases via credit card from ULI, we gather information needed to complete your order, such as your email, credit card number, expiration date and security code, your credit card billing address, and your credit card billing phone number. We use this data to process and fulfill your order. We do not use this data for any other purpose, nor do we retain this data after your order has been processed.

We use 128 bit secure sockets layer (SSL), the industry standard for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts **all of your personal information,** including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.

ULI is fully committed to data security. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information you provide to us online.

However, even after we receive personal information from you, we cannot guarantee that your information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed as a result of a breach of our commercially reasonable efforts or as a result of any other event beyond our reasonable control.  Also, please be aware that your email transmissions and/or other communications to ULI containing personal information may be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties and/or this Website may be subject to hostile network attacks or administrative errors.  Accordingly, ULI cannot and does not guarantee that your transaction information is completely secure and safe from such risks. **For the avoidance of doubt, we expressly disclaim any representation or warranty, whether express or implied, with respect to ensuring, guaranteeing or otherwise offering any definitive promise of security in connection with your personal information, transaction information or usage information.**  
**How do I opt out of e-mail communications?**

You can decline to receive most e-mail notifications from ULI. Most e-mail offers that you receive from ULI will include an “unsubscribe” link that allows you to opt-out of subsequent emails from that category. However, you cannot opt out of e-mails that ULI sends relating to your membership, such as renewal reminders and acknowledgements of your payments, event registrations, etc.  You also may control your e-mail preferences via your online profile at my.uli.org  If you have questions about e-mail opt-outs  please contact us directly at [customerservice@uli.org](mailto:enews@uli.org) or call toll free 800-321-5011 and tell us which e-mail communications you do not wish to receive.

**Who else has access to my member record?**

District Council and Product Council chairs have access to listings of members of their groups via the Internet. ULI members can access a limited amount of contact information about other members via the online Member Directory. Certain ULI staff can access member records via our member database to manage our membership programs. We recognize the responsibility that comes with handling information and we apply security measures to safeguard information about our members.

**Are there any restrictions on members’ use of the directory?**

Yes. Members are prohibited from using any directory listing for commercial or promotional purposes. Directory listings are provided to foster personal communication between two members, not for mass mailings or spam (unsolicited e-mail).

**How do I change my contact information? Bio?**

You may update or change information in your membership profile by logging into your profile at my.uli.org For other questions related to updating or changing your membership information, please send e-mail to [customerservice@uli.org](mailto:reliance@uli.org) or call +1-800-321-5011.

**Does ULI sell its mailing list?**

No. ULI will exchange mailing lists with carefully screened organizations to assure that members have the widest knowledge of available opportunities for continuing education, conferences, conventions, meetings, publications, technical services, and other topics likely to be of interest and value. To that end, ULI will exchange its associate member mailing list, on a name for name basis, with organizations publishing information or sponsoring events that are related primarily to real estate development and land use planning. ULI will at its sole discretion determine the acceptability of information that falls within the categories described above.

It is ULI’s policy that such promotions should not be political in nature, should not solicit donations, and should not contravene ULI policies or contain information that would allow a recipient to identify the identity or sources of the list.

**Miscellaneous—** This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the District of Columbia.  If any part of this Privacy Policy is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of this Privacy Policy shall continue in force and effect.

**We want to hear from you**

ULI welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Please send e-mail to [customerservice@uli.org](mailto:customerservice@uli.org).
